Guide to The Edward Streeter Papers 1909-1976 MSS 39 MSS.039
Fales Library and Special Collections
Edward Streeter Papers
1909-1976
Fales Library and Special Collections
Streeter, Edward, 1891-1976
MSS.039
14.5 Linear Feet in 22 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 5 oversize flat boxes, and 1 record carton
Edward Streeter (1891-1976), whose successful banking career did not prevent him from writing two of the most popular novels of his time, 'Dere Mabel' and 'Father of the Bride.' The collection includes manuscripts, correspondence, business materials, periodicals and ephemera.
Provenance
Edward Streeter presented his papers to the Fales Library in 1964.The gift included first editions of Streeter's books and copies of his many magazine appearances as well as seven linear feet of correspondence, manuscripts, diaries, scrapbooks, photographs and other memorabilia. In the fall of 1990 four linear feet of additional material, donated by Streeter's two daughters, was integrated into the existing collection.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note:
Edward Streeter, 1891-1976, was born in New York City where he lived most of his life. He attended Harvard and upon graduation (1914) became a reporter for the Buffalo Express. He then served in World War I attaining the rank of first lieutenant. Returning from the War, Streeter went on to a series of positions in the financial sector: Bankers Trust, Assistant Vice-President (1921-1929); Blake Brothers, Stock Broker, (1929-1930); 5th Avenue Bank (Bank of New York), Vice-President (1931-1956). Coincident with his success in the financial sector, Streeter wrote humorous fiction that achieved great popularity. His novel, 'Father of the Bride' (1949), was a best seller and was made into a motion picture starring Spencer Tracy and Elizabeth Taylor. Other notable works by Streeter are: 'Dere Mable' (1918); 'Mr. Hobb's Vacation' (1954); 'Ham Martin, Class of '17' (1969). Streeter was also a frequent contributor to numerous popular periodicals and was active in Harvard alumni activities.
Sources:
"Streeter, Edward, 1891-". Contemporary Authors. Detroit: Gale Research Company, 1967.
The Edward Streeter Papers; MSS 39; Fales Library and Special Collections, New York University Libraries.
Scope and Content Note
The Edward Streeter Papers are a part of the Fales Library, New York University. The Fales Library is the primary special collections division of the NYU libraries, housing over 200,000 volumes of English and American literature from 1700 to the present. Strengths of the collection include the development of the English and American novel, with an emphasis on the Gothic and the Victorian novel.
SERIES DESCRIPTION
The Streeter Papers are arranged in three series.
Series One, Writings includes diaries, juvenilia, essays, speeches, novels, and some print material in brochures and pamphlets. Some pictorial material, such as stills from the motion pictue version of Streeter's novel, Father of the Bride, is included in this series.
Series Two, Correspondence usually includes carbons of Streeter's letters as well as the respondent's originals and is divided into three subseries: [A] General Correspondence arranged chronologically. Of particular interest here is a 1927 file dealing with the business affairs of Charles Lindbergh.[B] Personal Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by writer, including several letters from novelists John P. Marquand, Thornton Wilder, illustrator Gluyas Williams, and actors James Stewart and Spencer Tracy.[C] Business Correspondence is arranged by publisher, producer, or firm.
Series Three, Printed Material consists of magazine appearances of Streeter's works: scrap books of his early journalistic efforts and of Father of the Bride, Pomfret School annuals, photo albums, and drawings by Bill Breck, illustrator of Dere Mabel. Magazines are boxed in no set arrangement. A bibliography of periodical contributions by Streeter are included in an appendix.
Arrangement
Folders are generally arranged chronologically within each series. See "SERIES DESCRIPTION" for details.
The files are grouped into three series.
Missing Title
Series I: Writings
Series II: Correspondence
Series III: Printed Material
Oversize - Series I: Writings
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.; Diaries; Manuscripts for publication.; New York (N.Y.).; American literature -- 20th century.; Art, Modern -- United States -- 20th century.; World War, 1914-1918 |x Humor.; Magazines (Periodicals); World War, 1914-1918 |v Caricatures and cartoons.; Correspondence.; Marquand, John P. (John Phillips), 1893-1960; Ranney, Dudley P.; Smith, Isabel; Stewart, James, 1908-1997; Tracy, Spencer, 1900-1967; Williams, Gluyas, 1888-1982; Lindbergh, Charles A. (Charles Augustus), 1902-1974; Donovan, William J. (William Joseph), 1883-1959; Breck, G. William (George William), 1863-1920; Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975
- Series I: Writings
  - Subseries A: Diaries, Juvenilia, Short Pieces.
    - Autobiographical Sketch, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Diaries 1-3 (undated) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Diaries 4-7 (undated) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Diaries 8 (Sept-Oct 1917 and undated) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Diary (typescript), undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Juvenilia:"Nicholas School"c. 1905 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Juvenilia:"Harvard English Class"c. 1914 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Aboard the 8:10 [Collier's 1920 Aug 7] (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Preface to Along the Road by Tom Barber, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Annual Report [1962] (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Annual Report [American Management Assn. 1964] (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Babe ["by Randolph Hall"], undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Back to Nature and Back [Sept 1920] (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Book Reviews., undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Break the Glass and Pull Down the Hook. [Sept. ], undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Christmas is for the Children [Good Housekeeping, 1961-1962] (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - College Yard or Lumber Yard., undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Daily Except Sunday [1938] (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Death in the Evening., undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Don't Write Off Wisdom [Life Magazine, Sp. 1962] (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Every Man a Dictator., undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Executive Without Portfolio. [Redbook 1939] (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - The Fourth Bride [1965]. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Frail Conqueror., undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Golf., undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Good Night., undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - A Guy from Elba., undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - The Great Outdoorsman [Suburbia Today, June 1962]. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Harvard. Class of 1914. 25th Reunion. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - The Harvard I Remember [The Harvard Alumni Bulletin, March 24, 1951]. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Havard Revisited [1960] (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Hole in One., undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - How to Boil an Egg [1958]. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Introd. to How to Guess Your Age by Corey Ford [1950] (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - How to Hold a Wife., undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Including One Jump., undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - It Must be the Bank's Fault [Redbook 1940]. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Keep Moving Please [1966]. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Knowledge is Power [Morrow's Almanac]., undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - The Laughing Horse of Gallup Street., undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Listen, Doctor., undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - The Log of the Namoa., undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Mary, Mary, Quite Contrary [Metropolitan 1922]. (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Memorandum on Sheldon Pennoyer [1958]. (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Memorial: Francis Berger Trudeau [1957]. (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - The Men in Upper Ten [Nov. 1913]. (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Meshine [film script], undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Monkey Business., undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Mr. Britchett Stories., undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Mr. Hobbs Comes Alive [June 1962] (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - The New Dog..., undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - The Nitwit., undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - No Union Man Wanted., undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - A Nobleman from Nowhere., undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Nobody Pays Any Attention., undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Over a Dead Man's Chest., undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Parachute School., undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Pickwick Series., undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Pomfret School: Sept. 1907-June 1910 [1955]., 1907-1955 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - The Population of Upper Ten., undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Private Schools., undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - A Quiet Night [play]., undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Read to Me., undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Reading Guilt: Uneasy is the Hand That Holds the Book [1967]. (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - The Return of John Harvard [a play]., undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Ring Out Wild Bells [Redbook, 14 Feb 1940]. (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - The Rules of Child Welfare., undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Sam to Bibo [Redbook, 1934] (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Scandinavia Air Service., undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Scandinavia on Wheels., undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - See America Fast., undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Speak French Like a Native..., undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Squash and How to Play It., undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - The Story of City Center., undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - The Strange Case of Edwin Weatherspoon [1964]. (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Summer Leasing., undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Third Avenue--Where Did it Go?, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Thorny Laurels., undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - A Toast for Lampy and His Friends [1946]. (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Travel., undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - 'Twas the Night Before Christmas [1962]. (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - The University Library [1961]. (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Wake Up and Sleep [Redbook, 1939]. (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - What Did They Give Walt Whitman for Christmas? [Suburbia Today, Dec. 1964]. (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - What Harvard Means to an Old Grad [1957]. (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - What is Money?, undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - When Grandfather Reads a Story [1959]. (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Where Are They Now., undated (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Why Grandpa Can't Read [1962]. (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Why I Have So Little Time to Read., undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Preface to the Collected Drawings of Gluyas Williams., undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Wish I Might [1963]. (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Without Hands., undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Talk on "Writing" [1959]. (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - You Can't Run Away from Christmas., undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Unpublished Manuscripts A-R., undated (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Unpublished Manuscripts S-Z, Untitled., undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Subseries B: Major Works.
    Scope and Contents note
    NOTE: Box 8A. Contains speeches
    - Along the Ridge. [draft], undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Along the Ridge. [2nd draft], undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Along the Ridge., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Along the Ridge., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - As You Were, Bill [see also Dere Mabel]., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Bed Manners., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Chairman of the Bored [pp. 1-132]., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Chairman of the Bored [pp. 135-255]., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chairman of the Bored [pp. 256-332]., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Chairman of the Bored [final draft]., undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Chairman of the Bored [excerpts]., undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Daily Except Sunday., undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dere Mabel., undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Dere Mabel [later installments 1920s]. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Dere Mabel [synopsis of a play]., undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Dere Mabel [Redbook 1930s]. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Dere Mabel [misc. ], undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 18-22. Dere Mabel [musical version]., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Father of the Bride., undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Father of the Bride [Chap. 1-12]., undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Father of the Bride [Chap. 13-15]., undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Father of the Bride [editorial comments]., undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Father of the Bride [film]., undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Father of the Bride [radio publicity]., undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Father of the Bride [audition script]., undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Father of the Bride [dramatic versions]., undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Letters from a Home Made Father to his Son [Nos. 1-40]., undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Letters from a Home Made Father [Nos. 41-71]., undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - The Log of the Trade Wind [1926]. (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Merry Christmas, Mr. Baxter [brief descriptions]., undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Merry Christmas, Mr. Baxter [Merry Christmas Eve]., undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Merry Christmas, Mr. Baxter [T. V. version]., undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Mr. Hobbs Takes a Vacation [Chap. 1-16]., undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Mr. Hobbs Takes a Vacation [Chap. 17-23]., undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Skoal Scandinavia [pp. 1-147]., undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Skoal Scandinavia [pp. 148-301]., undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Skoal Scandinavia [final draft]., undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Speeches., undated (Box 8, Folder 42-43.)
    - Advice to Young Authors [NYU, Feb. 13, 1958]. (Box 8A, Folder 44)
    - Book and Author Lunch [Nov. 20, 1956]. (Box 8A, Folder 45)
    - The Centuryn Club of New York [Oct. 5, 1961]. (Box 8A, Folder 46)
    - Groton School [1959]. (Box 8A, Folder 47)
    - Harvard - Board of Governors [Nov. 19, 1953]. (Box 8A, Folder 48)
    - Harvard - 40th Reunion [1954]. (Box 8A, Folder 49)
    - Harvard Club - 88th Annual Dinner [Jan. 15, 1954]. (Box 8A, Folder 50)
    - Harvard - 50th Reunion [1964]. (Box 8A, Folder 51)
    - Miller & Rhoads Book/Author Dinner [Apr. 23, 1954]. (Box 8A, Folder 52)
    - New York Public Library [Oct. 24, 1956]. (Box 8A, Folder 53)
    - Norwegian Chamber of Commerce [May 5, 1953]. (Box 8A, Folder 54)
    - Pomfret School Class Day [1955]. (Box 8A, Folder 55)
    - Pomfret - Graduation Day [1955]. (Box 8A, Folder 56)
    - Pomfret - Award Dinner [Dec. 8, 1964]. (Box 8A, Folder 57)
  - Subseries C: Verse, Notes, Pictorial and Printed Material.
    - Verse., undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Notes., undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Letter to the Editor/Along the Ridge [1966]. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Dere Mabel [Breck illustrations]., undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dere Mabel: A Widow Can't be Too Careful [clippings]., undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Father of the Bride [photos]., undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Personal Photos., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Photos: Log of the Trade Wind., undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Photos: World War I., undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Misc. Pictorial., undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Printed Material: Dere Mabel., undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Play. Father of the Bride., undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Printed Material. Father of the Bride [includes Gluyas Williams illustration fornsr the New Yorker]., undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Harvard., undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Honors and Awards., undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Lincoln Center., undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Mexican Border, 1916-1917. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Pomfret School., undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Simon and Schuster Agreement., undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Social Groups., undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Re: various novels., undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - World War I., undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous., undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Works by Others., undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - War Diaries of A. W. Chauncey & A. B. Warfield., undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - The Battle of the Bonus. Pamphlets., undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - The Kind of Bank Joe and Mrs. Doakes Like [1956]. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Mr. Banks' Other Daughter., undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Mr. Robbins Rides Again., undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Notes on Retirement Book., undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Ms. Retirement Book., undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Ms. Untitled Book on "Money"., undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Untitled Manuscript., undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Ms. Window on America - Bibliography., undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Ms. Window on America: 1784-1969. (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Oversize: Series I
  Items were not categorized by subseries when initially processed.
  - Harvard: The Legend of Loravia [musical Score]., 1914 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Oakland Atletic Club [rules and diary]., 1906 (Box 12, Folder 1A.)
  - Schedule of Activities in France [1918-1919]. (Box 12, Folder 1B.)
  - Speak French Like a Native. Ms., undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Dere Mabel Notes., undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - What Did They Give Walt Whitman for Christmas., undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts., undated (Box 12, Folder 5-9.)
  - Dere Mabel. [Clipping], 1919 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Pamphlets., 1916-1961 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Unbroken Thread of Humor [Clipping, galley? from The New Yorker]., undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Printed Material. [Clippings], undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Speech to Harvard Club, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Speeches/Recordings. [(1) Reel, (1) cassette, (7) flexidisks], 1950-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Streeter Genealogy., 1927 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Unpub. Ms. Autobiography., undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Unpub. Ms. Autobiography., undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Chronological List of Articles and Speeches., undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Harvard Lampoon [notes]., undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Unpub. Ms. House on the Dunes [1st draft]., undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Ms. Keep Moving Please [McCall's 1965]. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Notes on Old Age Book., undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Ms. "O Rare Don Marquis" [Feb. 4, 1962]. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Ms. "The Off-Islanders" [July 11, 1956]. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Ms. You Can't Get Away from Christmas [McCall's 1964]. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper clippings., undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: Correspondence.
    - 1918-1925. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lindbergh, Charles A. Affairs., 1927 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1930-1938. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 1939-1949. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 1950-1951. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 1952-1953. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 1955-1956. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 1957-1959. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 1960-Oct. 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Nov. 1961-Feb. 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Mar. 1962-1963. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 1964-1967. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 1968-1969. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - 1970-1973. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - n. d., undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: Selected & Business Correspondence.
    Box 17A contains correspondence with Gluyas Williams.
    - Donovan, William J. - Troop I 50th Anniversary., undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Nunnally., undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Marquand, John P. 1948-1970. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Misc. Receipts - Anges Demarest [1881-1893]. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Ranney, Dudley P. 1935-1963. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Isabel 1938-1954. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Smith, Isabel 1955-1966. (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Stewart, James [1962]. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Streeter, William W. [regarding his death]., undated (Box 17, Folder 25-26.)
    - Tracey, Spencer., undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Wilder, Thornton [1936] (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Gluyas Williams. 1937-1949. (Box 17A, Folder 29)
    - Gluyas Williams. 1950-1958. (Box 17A, Folder 30)
    - Gluyas Williams. 1959-1967. (Box 17A, Folder 31)
    - Gluyas Williams. 1968-1974. (Box 17A, Folder 32)
    - Military Records 1918-1919. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Income Tax Information & Earnings Records., undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - The Bell Syndicate., undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - The Best Allenby Agency., undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Brandt & Brandt 1919-1955. (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Brandt & Brandt 1956-1975. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - CBS Radio., undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Collier's., undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - The Commentator., undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Cumbre Publishing., undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Dodd, Mead & Company., undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Doremus & Company., undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Doubleday & Company., undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Duttons, Inc., undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Everybody's Magazine., undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Fales Library., undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Father of the Bride., undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Good Housekeeping., undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - The Grand Magazine., undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Grombach Productions 1940-1941. (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Groton School 1959-1960. (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Harper & Bros/Harper & Row 1939-1954. (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Harper & Row 1955-1974. (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Harvard Lampoon., undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Harvard University 1953-1976. (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Henry Holt & Company., undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Herald-Tribune., undated (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Hillman Periodicals., undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Jarrolds Publishers., undated (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Ladies Home Journal., undated (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Life Magazine., undated (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - J. B. Lippincott Company., undated (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Loews, Inc. 1958 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer., undated (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - MGM-TV., undated (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Misc. Magazines 1943-1967. (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Misc. Newspapers., undated (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - The New York Times., undated (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Newsweek., undated (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Pomfret School., undated (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - President's Professional Assn., undated (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - G. P. Putnam's Sons., undated (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Random House., undated (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Reader's Digest., undated (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - RKO Radio Pictures., undated (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - The Saturday Evening Post., undated (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Schaefler, Leon [attorney]., undated (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Sharp, Doris., undated (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Simon & Schuster 1938-1950. (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Spadea Syndicate., undated (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Frederick A. Stokes Company 1918-1941. (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - This Week Magazine., undated (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation., undated (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - The Vanguard Press., undated (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - Warner Bros. Circuit., undated (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - The World Publishing Company., undated (Box 19, Folder 88)
- Series III: Printed Material
  - Subseries A: Printed Material.
    - Collier's Magazine: 1920: June 12, 26 "Aboard the 8: 10" (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_a5848103cfe209fc5ad24e391c97ae3f)
    - Collier's Magazine: 1920: July 17-24 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_1bbae1b43dcc6f2cef59b852a294359f)
    - Collier's Magazine: 1920: August 7 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_861439161680b63523814a25d8d7c7f2)